it's now time for tonight's hasht
[Applause]
Wars Kate four cannibals in a funeral
yes
points He's Just Not That Into
calingus points Jim uh kidney failure to
launch yes points Kate when Harry killed
Sally yes points Jim uh how to lose a
pregnancy in 10 days
points AR never been
fist F Kate WS yay 40-year-old anal
[Laughter]
[Applause]
virgin Doug Benson fish
[Laughter]
farts both spelled with a pH yes F SP f
f
bar
raisin that image yes I like raisins
points Doug uh banana spliff yes points
eser Cherry Springer Cherry Springer yes
points well done Doug Benson chocolate
chip cookie Doug
yes what the ice cream that's so high it
eats itself
Esther mint chocolate cheny yes points
yeah points Greg Baron uh I want to go
with corn nuts hang on caveat it's not
Corn Nut The Corn Nut it's the nuts of
the band
corn the really awful yeah Point done
people don't know this but Chubby Hubby
was originally called
fat
what guy brandom rear Enders Game yes
boys yeah and on that note you oron
Scott
Card Alli Wong Indiana Jones and the
Temple of punon yes
pun run uh Doctor Who's that in my
[Laughter]
butt why is it bigger on the
inside points to Ron funches guy brandom
triple X-Men first ass yes oh wow wow
nice next next Ron fahit 69 yes Point gu
uh my dick the
Gathering it's star Zack Eon star Zack
Efron point for that yes Bo R punches
lord of the r yes bu Allie Bill NY the
Science Guy on
guy on this guy on guy BR nice B run
punches uh Men in Black Men in Black
[Laughter]
man these are So Meta Bo R bunches guy
Dr really strange love yes buch it got a
snort you get 100 points Ron uh Star
Wars but with
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
fing yes Jen Fel Williamsburg yeah nice
oh good one points uh Morgan man
boobs PA Hopkins uh Suns and Roses the
Mumford and Suns and Guns and Roses
tribute mash up
man and I say Welcome to the
Jungle uh Jen Foster the People's Choice
Awards yes points Morgan hit it Morgan
oh sorry Paul uh Adel deim
yeah points Morgan uh tan and Sarah
Palin
yes J Kirkman Lana Del Rachel Ray yes
excellent point follow uh ketcha which
is like Kesha but with a scent sign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
instead